Washingtoniana Vertical File Index VF.001 VF.001
Test
- Restaurants. Vincenzo
- Restaurants. Vivande Ristorante
- Restaurants. W. H. Bone and Co.
- Restaurants. Waffle Shop
- Restaurants. Wagshal's Deli
- Restaurants. Water Gate Inn
- Restaurants. Watergate Terrace
- Restaurants. Wearley's
- Restaurants. Wendy's
- Restaurants. West End Café
- Restaurants. White Elephant
- Restaurants. White House Connection
- Restaurants. White Tiger
- Restaurants. Whitlow's
- Restaurants. Wild Oats
- Restaurants. William's
- Restaurants. Wisey's
- Restaurants. Xing Kuba
- Restaurants. Yanni's
- Restaurants. Yanyu
- Restaurants. Yenching Palace
- Restaurants. Yes
- Restaurants. Zaytinya
- Restaurants. Zebra Room
- Restaurants. Zed's Ethiopian Cuisine
- Restaurants. Zengo
- Reston SEE Metropolitan District. Virginia. Reston
- Restoration SEE Business, Individual. Restoration
- Resurrection Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. Resurrection
- Retirement SEE District Employees. Retirement; Retirement, Board of; Police. Salaries and Retirement
- Retirement, Board of
- Retrocession SEE ALSO Arlington County. Retrocession; Retrocession. Maryland
- Retrocession. Maryland SEE ALSO Arlington County. Retrocession
- Revenue Sharing SEE Taxation. Revenue Sharing
- Revolutionary War
- RFK Stadium SEE Stadiums. RFK
- Rich's SEE Stores. Rich's
- Right to Read
- Riots
- Riots. 1968 (April) SEE ALSO Description (by date)
- Riots. 1968 (April). Pamphlets
- Riots. Race Riots, 1919
- Riparian Rights SEE Potomac River. Riparian Rights
- Riverfest SEE Potomac River. Riverfest
- Riverside Stadium SEE Stadiums. Riverside
- Rivlin Commission SEE Finances. Commission on Budget and Financial Priorities
- Robert H. Terrell Law School SEE Colleges and Universities. Robert H. Terrell Law School
- Robert F. Kennedy Funeral SEE Funerals. Kennedy, Robert F. 1968
- Rock Creek (by date) SEE ALSO Parks. Rock Creek
- Rock Creek Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. Rock Creek
- Rock Creek Nature Center
- Rock Creek Park SEE Parks. Rock Creek
- Rock Creek Park Estates SEE Residential Sections. Rock Creek Park Estates
- Rock Creek Parkway SEE Streets. Rock Creek Parkway
- Rock Music SEE Music. Rock
- Roll Call SEE Newspapers. Roll Call
- Roller Derby SEE Sports. Roller Derby
- Rooming and Boarding Houses (by date)
- Rooming and Boarding Houses. Saint Catherine's Residence for Business and Professional Women
- Roosevelt Funeral SEE Funerals. Roosevelt
- Roosevelt Memorial SEE Memorials. Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
- Ropewalks SEE Business, Individual. Ropewalks
- Roses. Flower Shows SEE Flowers. Flower Shows. Roses; Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Potomac Rose Society
- Rosslyn SEE Metropolitan District. Virginia. Rosslyn
- Round Top SEE Residential Sections. Round Top
- Routes SEE Buses. Routes
- Rowing SEE Sports. Rowing
- Rugby SEE Sports. Rugby
- Ruhani Satsang SEE Churches. Ruhani Satsang
- Rumor Control
- Runaways and Missing Persons SEE ALSO Police. Missing Persons Bureau
- Running SEE Sports. Running
- Russian Churches SEE Churches. Eastern Orthodox. Russian
- Safety SEE ALSO Automobiles. Safety; Subways. Safety; Traffic. Safety
- Safety Director SEE ALSO Public Schools. Safety Director
- Safety Patrols SEE Public Schools. Safety Patrols
- Safeway SEE Stores. Safeway
- Saint Joseph's Seminary of Washington, D.C. SEE Colleges and Universities. Saint Joseph's Seminary of Washington, D.C
- Saint Paul's College SEE Colleges and Universities. Saint Paul's College
- Salaries SEE Commissioners. Salaries; District Employees. Salaries; Fire Department. Salaries; Police. Salaries and Retirement; Public Schools. Salaries; Public Schools. Teachers. Salaries; Wages
- Sales Tax SEE Taxation. Sales
- Sallie Mae SEE Businesses, Individual by name. Student Loan Marketing Association (Sallie Mae)
- Saloons
- Saltz Brothers SEE Stores. Saltz Brothers
- Salvation Army (by date)
- Sand and gravel SEE Business, Individual. Sand and Gravel
- Sanitation Department (by date)
- Sarah G. Bowerman Memorial Association SEE Public Library. Sarah G. Bowerman Memorial Association
- Sasha Bruce Youthworks SEE Group Home. Sasha Bruce Youthworks
- Saturday Half Holiday SEE District Employees. Saturday Half Holiday
- Scandals SEE District Employees. Scandals
- Scarlet Oak SEE Trees. Official Tree
- Scholarships (by date)
- Scholarships. Project Excellence
- School Crossing Guards SEE Police. School Crossing Guards
- Schools Division SEE Public Library. Schools Division
- Schools SEE Music. Courses and Schools; Parochial Schools; Private Schools; Public Schools
- Science and Scientists (by date)
- Scientology SEE Churches. Scientology
- Scott Circle SEE Circles and Squares. Scott Circle
- Scott Memorial SEE Memorials. Scott, Winfield
- Scottish Rite Temple (16th and S Sts., NW) (by date) SEE ALSO Masonic Temples; Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Masons
- Scrap and Waste Material SEE Business, Individual. Scrap and Waste Material
- Sea Cadet Corps SEE Military Organizations. Sea Cadet Corps
- Seal (D.C.) (adopted 1871)
- Search and Seizure (by date) SEE ALSO Crime and Criminals
- Sears, Roebuck SEE Stores. Sears Roebuck
- Seasons
- Second Division Memorial SEE Memorials. Second Division (Flaming Sword)
- Secret Service SEE White House. Secret Service
- Secretarial Services SEE Business, Individual. Secretarial Services
- Secretary, D.C. Office of the
- Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Building (500 N. Capitol)
- Securities Brokers and Dealers SEE Business, Individual. Securities Brokers and Dealers
- Security Systems and Equipment SEE Business, Individual. Security Systems and Equipment
- Segregation and Discrimination SEE Blacks. Segregation and Discrimination; Public Schools. Segregation and Discrimination; Race Relations
- Self-Realization Fellowship SEE Churches. Self-Realization Fellowship
- Seminaries SEE Colleges and Universities. Specific name of school; Private Schools. Specific name of school
- Senior Citizens Program (by date) SEE ALSO Old Age. Senior Citizens Centers
- Sentences SEE Courts. Sentences
- September 11, 2001 SEE Terrorism. September 11, 2001
- Service Area Committees (by date)
- Services Relating to Adult Literacy Programs SEE Public Library. Services Relating to Adult Literacy Programs
- Sesquicentennial Celebration SEE ALSO Bicentennial D.C.; Centennial Celebration
- Settlements
- Settlements. A-Z
- Settlements. Anne B. Johenning Baptist Center
- Settlements. Baker's Dozen SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Baker's Dozen
- Settlements. Baptist Center SEE Anne B. Johenning Baptist Center
- Settlements. Barney Neighborhood House (by date)
- Settlements. Christ Child Society Settlement Home
- Settlements. Colored Social Society
- Settlements. Fides House
- Settlements. Friendship House (by date)
- Settlements. Georgetown Children's House
- Settlements. Good Samaritan (Downey House)
- Settlements. Hampshire House
- Settlements. Hollyday House
- Settlements. Hospitality House
- Settlements. Juanita K. Nye House
- Settlements. Noel House
- Settlements. Northwest
- Settlements. Opportunity House
- Settlements. Pamphlets
- Settlements. Southeast House (by date)
- Settlements. Southwest House
- Settlements. Teen Haven
- Settlements. Three Leaf Clover Youth Settlement
- Settlements. Unity House
- Sewage Disposal (by date)
- Sewage Disposal. Chemical Treatment
- Sewage Disposal. Legislation
- Sex
- Sex Crimes SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Sex Crimes
- Shadow Representative SEE Politics and Government. Shadow Representative
- Shadow Representative Elections SEE Politics and Government. Shadow Representative. Elections
- Shadow Senator SEE Politics and Government. Shadow Senator
- Shadow Senator Elections SEE Politics and Government. Shadow Senator. Elections
- Shakespeare Library SEE Folger Shakespeare Library
- Sharecroppers' Camp (1966)
- Sharpe Health School SEE Public Schools. Special Education. Sharpe Health School
- Sharpening and Repair SEE Business, Individual. Sharpening and Repair
- Shaw SEE Residential Sections. Shaw
- Shaw/Dupont Community Center SEE Community Center. Shaw/Dupont (proposed)
- Shepherd Memorial SEE Memorials. Shepherd, Alexander R.
- Shepherd Park SEE Residential Sections. Shepherd Park
- Shepherd Park Branch SEE Public Library. Branches. Shepherd Park
- Sheridan Circles SEE Circles and Squares. Sheridan
- Sherman Memorial SEE Memorials. Sherman, William T.
- Shevchenko Memorial SEE Memorials. Shevchenko, Taras
- Shipping and Shipping Brokers SEE Business, Individual. Shipping and Shipping Brokers
- Shoe Repair SEE Business, Individual. Shoe Repair
- Shooting SEE Sports. Shooting
- Shoplifting SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Shoplifting
- Shopping Centers (by date)
- Shopping Centers. Georgetown Park
- Shuttle Buses SEE Buses. Shuttle Buses
- Sickle-cell Anemia SEE Diseases. Sickle-cell Anemia
- Sidewalks SEE Streets. Sidewalks
- Sign Making SEE Business, Individual. Sign Making
- Signal 13 SEE Newspapers. Signal 13 (Police)
- Signals SEE Traffic. Signals
- Silkworms
- Silver Spring SEE Metropolitan District. Maryland. Silver Spring
- Silversmiths SEE Business, Individual. Silversmiths
- Sister Cities (Bangkok, Beijing, Dakar)
- Sixth Marines SEE Armory. Sixth (6th) Marines
- Skating and Hockey SEE Sports. Hockey; Sports. Skating and Hockey
- Skiing SEE Sports. Skiing
- Skyline
- Slavery and Emancipation SEE Blacks. Slavery and Emancipation
- Sloane SEE Stores. Sloane
- Slogan (D.C. Official)
- Slums (by date) SEE ALSO Alleys; Housing; City Planning
- Small Business SEE Business. Small Business
- Small Claims Court SEE Courts. Small Claims Court
- Smithsonian Institution SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Smithsonian Associates
- Smithsonian Institution (by date)
- Smithsonian Institution. African American Museum (proposed)
- Smithsonian Institution. Anacostia Neighborhood Museum and Center for African American History and Culture
- Smithsonian Institution. Arts and Industries Building
- Smithsonian Institution. Donald W. Reynolds Center for American Art and Portraiture SEE Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American Art; Smithsonian Institution. National Portrait Gallery
- Smithsonian Institution. Festival of American Folklife SEE Festivals. Folklife
- Smithsonian Institution. Freer Gallery of Art (by date) SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. Sackler Gallery
- Smithsonian Institution. Hirshhorn Collection (proposed)
- Smithsonian Institution. Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (by date)
- Smithsonian Institution. Legislation
- Smithsonian Institution. National Air and Space Museum
- Smithsonian Institution. National Collection of Fine Arts (by date) SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American Art
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of African American History and Culture SEE Smithsonian Institution. African American Museum (proposed)
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of African Art
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American Art SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. National Collection of Fine Arts; Smithsonian Institution. National Portrait Gallery
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American History SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of History and Technology
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of History and Technology (by date) SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American History
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of Natural History (by date)
- Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of the American Indian
- Smithsonian Institution. National Portrait Gallery SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. National Museum of American Art
- Smithsonian Institution. National Postal Museum
- Smithsonian Institution. National Zoo SEE Zoos. National Zoological Park
- Smithsonian Institution. Pamphlets
- Smithsonian Institution. Renwick Gallery
- Smithsonian Institution. Sackler Gallery SEE ALSO Smithsonian Institution. Freer Gallery of Art
- Smithsonian Institution. Smithson, James
- Snakes and Reptiles SEE ALSO Animals
- Sniper SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. By Name. Muhammad, John A. and Malvo, Lee Boyd
- Snow (by date)
- Soap Box Derby SEE Racing. Soap Box Derby
- Soccer SEE Sports. Soccer
- Social action SEE Business, Individual. Social action
- Social Life (by date) SEE ALSO Blacks. Social life; Embassies and Legations; Public Library. Social Life; White House. Social life
- Social Life. Blacks SEE Blacks. Social Life
- Social Life. President's Birthday Celebration (by date)
- Social Life. President's Birthday Celebration. Pamphlets
- Social Life. Public Library SEE Public Library. Social Life
- Social Life. Weddings (by date)
- Social Life and Custom SEE Description (by date)
- Social Planning (by date) SEE ALSO Anti-Poverty Programs; Birth Control; Neighborhood Legal Services Project; Public Schools. Attendance
- Social Planning. Community Leadership Training Project
- Social Planning. Preschool
- Social Planning. Youth (by date) SEE ALSO Public Schools. Attendance
- Social Problems (by date) SEE ALSO Anti-Poverty Programs; Birth Control; Citizens Information Service; Crime and Criminals; Narcotics; Prostitution; Race and Race Relations; Social Planning
- Social Security (by date) SEE ALSO Pensions
- Social Security Building SEE Health, Education and Welfare Buildings. Wilbur J. Cohen Federal Building
- Social Service SEE ALSO Charities; Public Welfare
- Social Service. Legislation
- Social Service. Pamphlets
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations (by date) SEE ALSO Drama Clubs; Citizens Associations; Civic Associations; Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Name of Specific Organization
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. A
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Aaron Burr Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. AARP (American Association of Retired Persons)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Academy of General Practice
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Accuracy in Academia Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Acoustical Society of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. ACT
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. ACT-UP (AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Action to Rehabilitate Community Homes
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Active Retirees
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Administrative Women in Education
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Adopt Minority Children
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Adoptee - Birthparent Support Network
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Adult Education Association of Greater Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Adventurers Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Advertising Club of Metropolitan Washington (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Advisory and Learning Exchange
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Aero Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Africa House
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. African American Photographers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. African American Women's Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. African Safari Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Africare
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Afro Academic Cultural Technological and Scientific Olympics (ACTSO)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Afro American Bicentennial Corporation
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Afro American Historical and Genealogical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Afro-Caribbean Youth Center, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Agricultural History Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Agriculture Camera Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Agriculture Employees Recreation Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. AHEAD (Adventures in Health, Education and Agricultural Development)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Aides to All Charities
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Air Corps Women's Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Air Line Traffic Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Air Scouts of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Albert Deutsch Center
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alcoholics Anonymous SEE ALSO Alcoholism; Liquor. Alcoholics
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alexander Graham Bell Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alfalfa Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alibi Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. All Peoples Congress
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. All States Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Allied Architects of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Allied Florists of Greater Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Allied Organizations of the District of Columbia
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Almas Temple
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alpha Wives
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alumni and Alumnae (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alumni and Alumnae. Columbia University Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alumni and Alumnae. Columbian Women of George Washington University
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alumni and Alumnae. Princeton Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alumni and Alumnae. Vassar Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Amara Civic Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American First Committee
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Academy of Pediatrics
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Art Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Artists Professional League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association for the Advancement of Atheism
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Advertising Agencies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Engineers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Hospital Social Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Medical Social Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Museums
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Retired Persons (AARP)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Social Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Teachers of French
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of Teachers of Spanish and Portuguese
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Association of University Professors
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Automobile Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Bankers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Business Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Business Women's Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Cancer Society (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Ceramics Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Chamber of Agriculture
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Chemical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Child Health Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Citizens Committee
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Civic Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Coalition of Patriotic Societies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American College of Dentists
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Colonization Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Committee for Spanish Freedom
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Council for Judaism
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Council of Learned Societies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Council on Human Rights
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Culinary Association and American Institute of Chefs
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Diabetes Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Dietetic Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Enterprise Institute
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Equity Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Federation of Arts
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Field Service
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Fighter Ace Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Forestry Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Friends of German Freedom
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Friends of Hebrew University of Jerusalem
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Friends of the Middle East
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Friends of the West Indies Federation
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Genetic Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Gold Star Mothers, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Guild of Organists SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Music. American Guild of Organists
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Heart Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Historical Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Accountants
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Adult Education
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Architects (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Banking
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Cooperation
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Decorators
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Electrical Engineers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Men's and Boys' Wear
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Institute of Pharmacy
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Jewish Congress and American Jewish Committee
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American League for Peace and Democracy
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Legion, District Department (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Legion, National Headquarters
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Library Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Lung Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Medical Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Merchant Marine Library Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Meteorological Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Military Institute
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Nature Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Newspaper Guild
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Newspaper Women's Club (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Pharmaceutical Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Planning and Civic Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Political Science Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Public Relations Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Rescue Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Rheumatism Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Road Builders Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Rocket Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Savings and Loan Institute
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Society for Public Administration
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. American Society for the Relief of Russian Exiles